これら４つの要素を 四大行と呼び あらゆる強さを得るのに 不可欠な要素だ これにより　肉体は強靭となり 若さも保つ 「纏」　念オーラを 体の周囲に　とどめる技 「絶」　念オーラを完全に絶つ技 「練」　念オーラのエネルギーを 増大させる技
You didn't know?
「発」…　「練」で増大させた 念オーラを最終的に発する技
I'm saying that some unique humans
are overflowing with life energy.
念能力を使いこなすための 基礎になるのだ
You didn't know?
自身の気配を消したり 疲労回復に効果がある
I'm saying that some unique humans
are overflowing with life energy.
「念」の修行を禁止された ２か月が経過し ゴンはキルアと共に ウイングの前に呼び出されていた
Kite x And x Slots
ゴンくん　キルアくん
Kite, Gon, and Killua have advanced
今日からズシと共に 修行することになります。 ゴンくん　この２か月 よく約束を守りましたね。
deep within NGL, in search
of the Chimera Ant nest, and have arrived at a cliff
with peculiar openings.
誓いの糸のおかげです。
This is the Chimera Ant nest?
実は　何度も　誘惑に負けそうに なったんだけど
No.
この糸を見詰めていると 心が落ち着いて来るんです。 そういう「念」を 込めておきましたから。
They don't make their nests in holes. They use mud and feces to build them.
いや　ウソです。
Let's go.
えっ？ でもさ　何で 約束を守ったかどうか分かんの？
You'll understand once we're inside.
誓いの糸が 切れていないからですよ。 ゴンくん　久々ですが
There's no telling when or
from where they will attack.
「纏」をやってみてくれませんか？
Be on your guard.
いいの？ ええ。
Yeah, got it.
ヤッベ！　俺　やれるかな…
That other Chimera Ant
本当に久しぶりだ うまく　できるだろうか
completely concealed his presence.
全身のオーラが よどみなく流れてるっす！ 静かで　なだらかで それでいて　すごく力強いっす！
Let's go.
もちろん 高度に使いこなすためには
Is this place...
努力を怠ってはいけませんがね。 でも　前より すごく自然にできたよ。
Yes, it is NGL's hidden side. A drug factory.
全然　「纏」の練習なんて してないのに。
Exactly.
君が　毎日　心を鍛える修行を 続けた成果です。 さっ　左手を見てみなさい。 えっ？
This factory produces the ingestible drug D², which is spreading throughout the mainland.
あっ　切れてる！
There are probably nearby bila trees,
which produce its main ingredient.
君が約束を破って「念」を使ったら 切れるように結んであったのです。
Ironic given their claims as preservationists. They're making more than drugs.
私の「念」でね。
Look.
そんなことも　できるのか…
It's the same as the others.
ねぇ　ウイングさん ヒソカとカストロの試合　見た？ ええ　見ました。 ヒソカの能力って何なの？
I assume that only the NGL leaders
know the truth of this place.
切れた腕を飛ばしたり あんなこと　俺達でも　できるの？ うん　難しい質問だね。
The other members joined because they honestly loved nature.
ゴンくんは その対戦をビデオで見たかい？ ううん　まだだよ。
So this facility is the center
of NGL's underground.
あっ。
If it's empty...
じゃ　見ながら説明しましょうか。
Then Chimera Ants have wiped
out the NGL underground.
ここで　左手からオーラの糸が 出ているのが見えるかな？
What about their boss? He either escaped or was eaten.
オーラの糸？
Either way, it's bad news.
ええ　どうかな？
Huh? What do you mean? Shh!
ダ…　ダメだ。 全然　見えねえよ。
A few are around.
本当に　ここでヒソカの左手から オーラの糸が出てんの？ ええ　ヒソカは自分のオーラを 限りなく見えにくくする技を
They're slowly approaching
through the middle tunnel.
ここで使っています。
There are more in the left and right tunnels.
「隠」といいます。
How far away can you search?
「隠」を使えば　強いオーラでも 相手には見えなくなります。
Everything within a forty-five meter radius.
これに対抗するには 「練」で生み出したオーラを
F-Forty-five meters?
目に集中させる「凝」を使うのが 最も有効です。
Depending on physical and mental condition,
I can increase that by a few meters.
以前　ゴンくんが ギド戦でやった方法でも
Here they come.
自分は　どうしたらいいっすか？ ズシ　君の力なら　もう ヒソカの「隠」を見破れるはずです。
Keep it down, you two.
自分が…？
Who are you guys?
２人の前で 「練」を見せてあげなさい。
How dare you intrude on my turf?
オ…　オッス！
Help... Please help us!
「練」！
Oops, didn't mean to do that.
すごい力強さだ！
Oh, well.
大きさは 俺達と同じくらいだけど
I'm getting bored with these guys.
オーラが 充満しているのが分かる
Guess I'll get rid of Rover, too.
「凝」！
Stop! Kite...
さぁ　この場面のヒソカの体から オーラが見えるかい？
Don't move carelessly. There's more than one enemy.
ハァ！　ハァハァ…。
Bye-bye.
ホントに見えたっす！
H-Hel—
オ…　オッス！ ありがとうございます。 今は　持てる力の全てを 「凝」に注いで
Don't look away. If they shoot a projectile your way,
you won't be able to see it.
修練を積めば　「凝」を行いながら 戦えるようになりますよ。 分かりましたね？ まずは　「練」の習得。
I've got it. You three will be my new dogs.
そして　応用技の「凝」を覚える。 そうすれば　ヒソカの能力が 一体　どんなものか 答えは おのずと　見つかるはずです。
Chimera Ants have always been aggressive, but it seems consuming malicious humans
has made them even more evil.
そして　ヒソカと同じ能力を 使えるようになるか
Huh? What do you mean? Phagogenesis.
その答えは　イエスでもあり ノーでもあります。 ヒソカの能力が何であれ
If we don't deal with them here,
many more will die!
ですが　念能力は　その人の個性に 大きく影響されます。
Capture them!
一人一人　好きなことや 得意な分野が違うように
I'll take the one in back.
「念」にも 得手　不得手があるのです。
You boys will have to deal
with the two rushing us.
真剣に「念」を極めたいなら
Right! Got it.
誰かの能力を マネしようとするのではなく
Do not hesitate. You must fight to kill.
まず　自分の資質を 見極めることが大切です。
Bring it!
オッス！ オッス！ オッス！
Ha, take this.
キルアくんの 戦闘準備期間の最終日は…
My unblockable Thousand Punches!
さっきのズシの「練」 すごかったね。
That was close.
しばらく休んでいるうちに すっかり　差をつけられちゃった。
You have more power than I expected.
いやいや　自分は　まだまだっす！
These guys are really tough.
ねぇ　さっきの修行　復習しない？
They have the hard shells of insects,
combined with human agility...
そうだな じゃあ　ゴンの部屋　行こうぜ。 うん。
What's on your mind now?
キルア　ズシ。
First comes rock... What?
あんたらも　しつこいなぁ 嫌われるよ　そんなんだと。
You'll be roving around the land of the
dead in no time, so I'll call you Rover!
まぁ　そう　邪険にせず いつ戦うのか教えなよ。
Been a while since I flipped my switch on.
フン…　新入り狙い専門の 連中らしくってよ 俺らと戦って 勝ち星　稼ぐつもりなんだぜ。
Damn you!
俺ら　結構　焦ってんだよ。
Curse you!
そろそろ　締め切りでね… ねぇ　戦おうよ。
Take this!
ここでね。
Fool!
俺は６月１０日に 戦闘日を指定する。
This is the poisonous one! Well?
おい　ゴン！ それじゃあ　ダメだね。
How does it feel as the poison
spreads through your body?
俺の締め切りが ５月２９日なんだよね。
Does it feel good?
その日にしなよ。
Very effective.
てめぇの都合なんか知るか　バカ 行こうぜ！
Once I drug him enough,
we'll have a human dog.
ゴンちゃん！
Are you done over there?
絶対　君と戦うからね。
Oh, not yet?
ゴン　相手にするな。
How...
どうするんだ？ 無理やり　やらせるさ。
My body is immune to poison.
ヘヘっ。
Ah, I see. If you behave, I'll kill you fast.
体内に エネルギーをためるイメージ
It just means that I was weaker.
蓄えた　その力を一気に　外へ！
She let that cheap act fool her.
じゃあ　また明日っす。 じゃあね。
What is this power flowing from his body? Any closer, and I'll suffer considerable damage.
さてと…。
What's wrong? Are you getting scared?
フッ…。
is his fist!
体が…
I'll sacrifice my eight left
legs to block his punch, while using the right eight to grab him.
体が　動かない！
Then I can bite him and inject my venom!
声が…　息も!? 一体　何が…
Let's run a simulation...
頼むね。
This will work!
ああ。
It's just a punch. No matter how strong it is, if I'm prepared, I can take it!
やめとけよ
Hey, we should get started soon.
何か　たくらんでるとは 思ったけど
Wait a little longer.
こんな　セコいまねしなくても 俺が相手してやるよ。
Screw that! You don't have a choice in the matter.
心配しなくても 勝ちは譲るからさ。
Now, entertain me.
それでいいだろ？
Very well...
お前から１勝もらった後 ゴンちゃんとも戦うからね。
What... Why are you here?
ゴンと　やりたいなら あいつのスケジュールに合わせろよな。
This is my castle.
それなら　あいつは喜んで戦うぜ。
A king needs no reason to be in his castle.
これは約束だからな。
There are many drugs here
that emit strong odors.
ヘヘヘ…　ＯＫ！
I would expect you to avoid this place.
君達が戦ってくれるなら 俺達も　わざわざ こんなことはせずに済むしね。
Shut up... I like this place!
これから一緒に 登録しに行こうか。
What happened to the head of NGL?
そうしたら　こいつは 無傷で君に渡そう。
He would have been here. Beats me!
はいはい　いいっすよ。
He's probably inside the Queen's belly.
その代わり これが最初で最後だからね。
I'm going to build my own kingdom starting here.
「５月２９日」と…。 さっ　これでいいんだろ？ ああ。
Then I'll take control of the whole world. That will be impossible for a
boor who amuses himself
それじゃあ　返そうね。
by making dogs of humans.
よっと…。
Really now? I can't wait to strip you down and
put a collar around your neck!
えと　まぁいいや　やめとこ。
Damn!
もしもし　ゴンくんかい？
Huh?
それで　大体の事情は のみ込めるだろう？
Hey! Get down here! You only summon me when you're in trouble.
[TEL]　これから俺の言うことを 誰にも話さず
You'd better watch it.
実行してくれさえすれば
I don't have time for small talk.
明日から　また何事もなく ３人で修行ができるよ。
Hurry it up. Oh, really? You're so impatient.
ズシ…
Are you insulting me?
ゴンちゃんは　どうだった？
Damn, bad spin. What was that?
ＯＫだ ３０日で受けてくれたぜ。
I have no bad spins, bastard!
ヘヘっ　これで２勝か ボロい　ねぇ。
Die!
さぁ　いらっしゃい チケットあるよ！ さっき出たばっかの チケットもあるよ。
I'll pretend to attack, while I block his punch.
ゴン対サダソの一戦と
Then I grab him and bite.
こっちは キルア対サダソの一戦だ！
Here I go!
今　買っとかないと 後悔するよ！
Rock... Paper...
おっちゃん。 はいよ！
Just as I thought!
そのサダソって　片腕の奴か？
Block! Scissors!
ああ　能面みたいな面した 片腕の選手さ。
What?
こいつの　見えない左腕に 捕まったら最後だぜ。 別名　「新人つぶし」って呼ば…。
A-A sword? Impossible...
うっ！ あの野郎。
Where was he hiding that?
ゴン　お前　ここにいたのか？ う…　うん。
But this could be perfect.
キルアくん　昨夜は ズシが世話になったみたいだね。
I can pretend I've been defeated, then wait for an opening to bite him!
１５本だろ？　トランプへ１３本 スカーフへ１本
You must crush the head.
あと　うまく隠してるけど 右腕を投げてて　そこに１本。
And preferably, you'll kill
them quickly and quietly.
続きを…。
Oh, it's him!
ヒソカは ヒソカのオーラは　まるで
The thing that shot us. I got a slot machine in my mouth!
伸び縮みしてるみたいに 見えるな。
It goes from 1 to 9.
それとも　磁石みたいに 引き合う性質があるのか…。
Each number summons a different weapon. This is my Crazy Slot!
でないと　腕が　くっついたり
Don't forget the name!
顎めがけて　正確に飛んで来る 理由が説明できない。
Just go away.
恐らく　前者かな？
That's a strange power... It talks by itself?
粘着性のゴムみたいに オーラを駆使してるのか…。 それなら 奇術の大部分が説明できる。
Apparently. If it uses a slot machine, doesn't that mean you can't
choose your weapon? Yes, and I cannot
ふぅ…。 レベルが違い過ぎるっす いいでしょう　合格です！
change or get rid of the
weapon I receive until I use it.
しかし　参りましたね。
It's very aggravating.
まさか　２人とも　ひと晩で 「凝」をクリアしてしまうとは…。 ゴンもか？
In that case... Why did you come up with this power?
で　キルアくん 君も　課題はクリアしたから 早く試合がしたいってことかな？
We've lost the signal from Yunju's team. Were they killed?
い…　いや　別に 抜け駆けとかじゃなくて ほら 急にムラムラと戦いたくなって。 ああ　分かってる。
The signal indicated three enemies, and that they looked tastier than the others.
ゴン　お前も脅されていたのか
They must be rare humans.
実は　俺 もう　戦いたい日も決まってる。
And we have cause to fight.
５月２９日なんだ。 俺は５月３０日。
Isn't Yunju using that factory as a base?
いいでしょう。
So the rare humans should
still be near the factory.
私も　君達の上達ぶりを 見くびっていました。
Let's go! Tonight, we feast!
決戦日までの鍛錬は 全て　「纏」と「練」に充てなさい。
Feast!
修行と息抜きと睡眠時間は 等しく　とるようにね。 オッス！ オッス！
Both of your powers are much
easier to use than mine.
キルア。 ん？
Compared to that thing of yours? No kidding.
あいつら キルアも脅迫したんだね。 腹立つな。
Yeah. Gon, you appear to have incorporated
Enhancer, Transmuter, and Emitter
ああ…　でも　まぁ
abilities into your Rock-Paper-Scissors.
一番　気がかりだった 師匠の許しは得たし。 けど　あいつらが また同じようなことを
Yep, but my natural affinity
lies with Enhancer abilities.
ズシにして来たらと思うとさ…。
Killua used lightning.
Are you a Transmuter?
大丈夫。 心配いらない。
Yeah, but it's not that strong,
and I lose energy fast.
今日　キルアちゃんに勝って ６勝
Let's hurry. The nest is close.
動くと殺す。 「念」を使うと殺す 声を出しても殺す。
I can feel power rushing into me.
分かったら　ゆっくり目を閉じろ。 約束を破ったらどうなるか 分かったか？
My body is overflowing with energy!
分かったら　ゆっくり目を開けて 鏡の俺を見て　よく聞け。
What is this?! What's wrong?
二度と俺達の前に 汚ねぇ面　出すな。
Rammot is acting strangely. Rammot?
サダソ選手　時間切れ！ 不戦勝　キルア！
Well? Look at this!
キルアの不戦勝で幕を開けた 卑劣な３人組との戦い 類いまれな才能によって
Can you see that light, Peggy?
驚異のスピードで「念」を習得した ゴンとキルアの 天空闘技場での真のバトルが
What tremendous life energy...